The world, what a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with the
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?.
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart.
But I know the way the long moon's day.
A brand new world that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
The way the long moon's day.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
And though I travel far
from where my search began.
Over streets of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world I bear.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Some days I'm where I'll finally see
the light I will search for everywhere?.
Ah!
Ah! Joker, watch out!
Something's wrong with these things!
They aren't normal!
Ah!
What's wrong with this forest?
Yes!
It's his fault! Who's?
The south bird is him!
He's controlling the bugs!
He can control bugs and guide ships!
Shh! Quiet!
You guys hear anything?
Something but it sure
doesn't sound like any
bird to me up there what
are they boulders yeah?
It looks like an avalanche no you're
wrong they're bugs ladybugs big ones!
There's no end to them they just keep
popping up stupid crickets oh come
on you think you can Beat me do you
i wish those birds were as easy to
see as they are to hear a slug that
size needs A lot of salt how could you
think of cooking at a time like this
i'm not salt dissolved slugs idiot!
I'm sick of all this running!
Let's stand and fight!
Come on, you bugs!
Bring it on! No, Lucy!
This one's still in our history!
Fireflies! Pretty!
Roaches!
Pigs!
Oh, I'll say! Look at this!
That's a fine piece of gold!
No way.
You punks have no right to take that gold.
No right?
I'll show you what gives us the right!
Big shot!
Oh, you damn fool.
We're way stronger than
you and your pals, old man.
I'd say that alone gives us the right
to take what we want, when we want.
Don't you?
Come on, let's dance.
If you don't mind, I'm cutting in.
Amok Satori!
Palsy, Sargus, no!
I'm going to finish him off my way.
It's him again.
The one with those
spring-spring fruit powers.
Shoujo, run!
Get out of there now!
Spring!
Sniper!
No, Shoujo!
Old timer!
Look what he found! Gold!
A bell-shaped ingot!
Look, it's just like it
says here in the logbook.
Gold bells, the story's true.
We're done here.
Load up, let's go.
And as for you, old man, grow up.
This city of gold is just a fairy
tale that Lionel and dreamt it all up.
If you want to be a pirate in this
new era, you've got to wise up.
Your dreams will never come true, ever.
The city of gold does exist.
Hey guys take it easy.
My house is pretty small.
You know something junior.
A worthless little punk like you who
is too afraid to believe in dreams?
doesn't have the right
to call himself a pirate.
What was that?
It's like trying to find
a needle in a haystack.
We didn't even see one.
Well, we did,
but we could never get close enough to
grab it thanks to all those stupid bugs.
All we did was run.
So seven people couldn't catch one bird.
That's pathetic.
Come on, won't you get it together, guys?
You're one to talk.
We've been doing this for hours.
I don't think I can run anymore.
He just said, you morons
think you can catch us?
Ha! Good one.
Morons?
What nerve?
Hey, birdbrain, I'll give you a
good one right between your eyes.
I can grab it if I can see it.
Hey, Pops, we caught one of those birds!
Pops, what happened? Mashira!
Shoujo!
What the...
what happened here?
I've got a better question.
Who did this?
Hey, give me your hand.
Ah!
The Going Mary!
What happened to her?
Who did this?
When I find out they're going to be
sorry they ever laid a finger on her,
the savages! Damn it!
Sorry, kid. You're alive!
Don't try to move, okay?
Just take it easy.
I'm really sorry about this.
We did everything we could to
stop them, but it wasn't enough.
It just looked pretty pathetic.
Gotta get moving, though.
The ship's not going to patch itself up.
Hold on, Pops! Wait!
Tell us what happened first!
Who did this to you?
Calm down. It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
That doesn't matter anymore did
you have any luck finding a?
Look at that you got
yourself a south bird nice
job they're hard to catch
luffy crickets gold!
It's all gone.
That stuff it's junk
just forget it it doesn't
matter your dream is more
important we have to!
Get you to the night
forget it how can you say
that think about what it
took to get that gold?
10 years of diving to
the bottom of the ocean
subjecting your body to
all the pressures of!
The deep come on you can't
just shut up i'm serious
that gold and what happens
to it is our problem!
Got it your ship's in no shape to make it
to the knock-up stream
if we can get all the?
Satoyama Alliance crew here.
They'll have it fixed
and reinforced by morning
You'll still be able to set sail tomorrow
Listen everything will be all right.
We will send you to the sky.
I promise that old timer
Hey Luffy
That's Bellamy's mark
you want any help i'll
handle this one alone
luffy don't be stupid
we don't have time for
this we have to set sail in three hours if
i follow the coast will
that take me all the
way back to Mock Town
yes i believe it will
hey where are you going
don't be an idiot You
can't possibly take on
this Bellamy guy all
by yourself if you want
to stop him use this
Kid don't do it
I'll be back by morning guys
Wow looks like the old moons
right up there under the water
Guess my eyesight's really getting bad.
I better get my eyes check or I'm
gonna end up falling off this dock
Imagine that, a pirate
with bad eyesight. Me?
I think I'd rather lose one
eye than have two bad ones.
Least I'd get an eye patch.
A fancy one, too.
Hey, what do you know? A newspaper.
Must be the really early edition.
Huh?
This ain't no paper.
It's a stack of wanted posters. Oh, boy.
What is this town coming
to when no life's come out?
Number of fine upstanding
citizens like myself huh?
It's those spineless guys.
From this afternoon ha?
That Lead kid talking about the
island in the sky was a riot.
What was he worth 30 million?
Hmm.
I guess my eyes that really
is getting pretty bad.
So one ten one hundred one thousand
ten thousand one hundred thousand.
I think I'm gonna need
some reading glasses.
100 thousand what?
One million.
One hundred million.
Three hours Luffy.
That's all you've got!
If you take any longer.
We're gonna lose our
chance to go to Sky Island.
And it's gonna be all your fault!
He's in bad shape.
It looks like he's been diving
dangerously like this for years.
Coming up too quick.
And not giving the gas bubbles
enough time to fully dissipate.
All I'm doing is following what
I believe to be my destiny.
This is a battle between me and Nolan.
I'm really sorry, kid.
We did what we could to stop
them, but it wasn't enough.
Bellamy!
Those apes really cracked me up.
It was hilarious when they
were all bloody and had tears
and snot running down their
faces and started crying.
Oh, Timer!
If you really meant so much, they should
have done a better job of protecting him.
Right?
Yeah, those guys were so lame.
Hey, what did you expect?
The same thing would have happened
to anyone else as stupid as them.
Taking on a big-time pirate worth
55 million berries like Bellamy?
That's just insane.
Bad news!
This better be good.
Those guys!
The ones that were here
this afternoon, they...
Bellamy!
What on earth are you still doing here?
You, you've got to get
out of here this instant,
I'm serious, you're in terrible danger!
What are you talking about?
How am I in danger?
60?
100?
Those two together are worth $160 million!
The bounties are higher than your spell.
I mean, know what that means?
You're dead meat.
And so are we.
We were laughing at them.
I think we messed with the wrong people.
They'll kill us.
You think they remember what we look like?
We should get out of here now.
I've never heard of anyone having
a bounty worth 100 million before.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey!
All it takes to scare you big tough
guys are some little scraps of paper!
What, do you all have
empty sockets for eyes?
You saw their scrawny little leader!
Made it!
This is nothing but a sham!
Here I'll explain it to you morons!
See,
there are pirates like
these losers who fake their
own wanted posters just to
make a name for themselves!
The fakers win fights without
throwing a single punch!
Their enemies take one look at their
bogus bounties, turn tail and run!
Just like you sorry excuses for
pirates are doing right now!
You saw them. They're weak.
They didn't even fight back.
But now you're all scared.
Pathetic.
Thanks, Bellamy.
Hey, they almost pulled
one over on us, huh?
Yeah, he's right.
Besides,
someone with a bounty of 100 million would
have had to pull off
some pretty big capers.
He looked pretty young, if you ask me.
And if that kid's so wanted,
how come we've never seen his
picture in the papers before?
Good point.
I've never heard of any kid
in a Straw Hat, have you?
I was pretty scared
there for a moment, huh?
Bellamy!
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Well, speak of the devil, we
were just talking about you.
You got something you
want to say to me, kid?
I do.
Give back Pop's gold,
every bit of it, right now.